No one has your back like a bridesmaid.
Bride Hard is a action, comedy film directed by Simon West.
Sam is a secret agent whose toughest mission to date is pleasing her
bride-to-be best friend at a lavish destination wedding.
When a team of mercenaries crashes the party and takes the guests hostage, Sam is thrown into a fight
unlike any before — one where she can’t risk blowing her cover or ruining the big day.
As she takes on the bad guys in a high-stakes battle disguised as a fairy-tale
affair, she realizes the real threat might be closer than she thinks.
Sam, played by Rebel Wilson.
Betsy, played by Anna Camp.
Virginia, played by Anna Chlumsky.
Lydia, played by Da'Vine Joy Randolph.
Zoe, played by Gigi Zumbado.
Nadine, played by Sherry Cola.
Bride Hard is a 2025 American action comedy film directed by Simon West and written
by Shaina Steinberg, from a story by Steinberg and CeCe Pleasants.
It stars Rebel Wilson, Anna Camp, Anna Chlumsky, Da'Vine Joy
Randolph, Gigi Zumbado, Stephen Dorff, and Justin Hartley.
The film grossed $1.9 million and was panned by critics.
The film explores themes of mercenary, secret agent, female
friendship, imminent wedding, action comedy.
The tone is lighthearted.